{"data":[{"question":"Ms. Lin ___ a lot of great deeds for others in her life.","a":"did","b":"has done","c":"had done","d":"was doing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: The Simple Past can also be used to describe a habit which stopped in the past. It can have the same meaning as \"used to.\" To make it clear that we are talking about a habit, we often add expressions such as: always, often, usually, never, when I was a child, when I was younger, etc.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"They believed that by using computers the production of their factory ___.","a":"would greatly increase","b":"will greatly increase","c":"would be greatly increased","d":"has greatly increased","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Future tense in past: would + Verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"This guy ___ to have another try if he can get another chance.","a":"means","b":"has been meaning","c":"has meant","d":"is meaning","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Mean to do something: to intend to do something or intend that someone else should do something \n- Zero Conditional: used for habitual actions or accepted facts \n- It is created by if\/when + two clauses with the same tense in each clause. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The writer lived in Texas until she _________ to university.","a":"had been sent","b":"was sent","c":"had sent","d":"was sending","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (used with a duration which starts and stops in the past) + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Greg _________ a bad cold for a week and still can't get rid of it.","a":"has caught","b":"caught","c":"has had","d":"had caught","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Once you ___ a promise, you must carry it out.","a":"made","b":"is making","c":"have made","d":"had made","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: used to express finished action that has an influence on the present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Perhaps it will be a long time ___ from abroad.","a":"when you will come back","b":"when you come back","c":"that you come back","d":"before you come back","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple future , before + simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Tommy promised his parents that he ___ early but he _________ yet.","a":"should be; isn't arriving","b":"will be; hadn't arrived","c":"would be; hasn't arrived","d":"is; hasn't been arriving","answer":"3","explain":"\n- First blank: Future in the Past is used to express the idea that in the past you thought something would happen in the future\n- Second blank: present perfect: use the Present Perfect to say that an action which we expected has not happened","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"We ___ for long when a bad message came.","a":"drunk","b":"had drunk","c":"were drinking","d":"had not been drinking","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Present perfect continuous: We use the Past Perfect Continuous to show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The Norman's family, which ___ rather a smaller one, very fond of their new house.","a":"was, were","b":"were, were","c":"was, was","d":"were, was","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (the Norman's family) can be plural or singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}